<odoo>
  <data >
    <record id="en_employee_contract_template" model="ssc.create.template">
      <field name="name">English Employee Contract</field>
      <field name="sample_template">True</field>
      <field name="sample_image" type="base64" file="ht_pdf_report_creator/static/src/img/icon_8.png"/>
      <field model="ir.model" name="model_id" search="[('model', '=', 'hr.contract')]"/>
      <field name="body" type="html">
        <body >
          <center>
            <b style="font-size:28px;color:#000066;" align="center">
              <u>
                ${object.employee_id.address_id.company_name}
                <br></br>
                Human Resources Department
              </u>
            </b>
          </center>
          <br></br><br></br>
          <div style="float:left;width:100%;text-align:left;">

            <center>
              <b style="font-size:24px;">
                <u>
                  EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT
                </u>
              </b>
            </center>
            <br></br>

            <b style="font-size:18px;">
              this contract is hereby between 
              <br></br>
              ${object.employee_id.address_id.company_name} 
              <br></br>
              Hereinafter referred to as first party
              <br></br>
              and 
              <br></br>
              Mr. /Ms
              <br></br>
               ${object.employee_id.name} , 
              <br></br>
              Hereinafter referred to as Second party
            </b>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article One 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
              The Second party agrees to work for the First party in any place belonging to the second party , or any other capacity which is commensurate with it's qualifications 
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Two 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The employment period shall begin from the date 
               <br></br>
               ${object.date_start}
               <br></br>
                on which the Second party starts his work . and start to working for 
                <br></br>
               ${object.resource_calendar_id.hours_per_day} hours per day and continue for ONE Year, and can be renewed automatically for another period, unless it is terminated as provided herein.
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Three
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The first three-month period is a trial period during which both parties have the right to terminate the contract
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Four 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The first party undertakes to pay $ 1,000 per month as a basic salary to the second party, provided that discounts are deducted from it in the event that the second party breaches the agreed upon work regulations
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Five 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The second party is entitled to the stipulated price for 40 working hours during the week, starting from Sunday morning to Thursday evening
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Six 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The first party shall bear the expenses of medical treatment for the second party, except for the expenses of dental treatment and medical glasses
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Seven 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The second party is entitled to 30 days (calendar days) of paid annual leave, excluding official and sick leaves
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Eight 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               That the second party undertakes and adheres to the general customs and behaviors that are recognized and applicable by the first party and not cause any embarrassment or damage to the interests of the first party
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Nine 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               It is not permissible for the second party to work with another party related to the first party after the end of his service for a period of less than six months without the written consent of the first party.
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Ten 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               The first party undertakes to pay an end-of-service reward, which is half of the salary for every month the second party spends in service with the first party
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b>
                <u>
                  Article Eleven 
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
               This contract represents the entire agreement between the two parties and supersedes any other verbal or written agreement
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br><br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b style="font-size:18px;">
                <u>
                  First party
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
              Name :  
              <br></br>
              Signature:  
              <br></br>
              Date  
            </n>
            <br></br><br></br>

            <n style="font-size:16px;">
              <b style="font-size:18px;">
                <u>
                  Second party
                </u>
              </b>
              <br></br>
              Name :  
              <br></br>
              Signature:  
              <br></br>
              Date  
            </n>
          </div>
        </body>
      </field>
    </record>
  </data>
</odoo>